So,
所以
both you and I,
我们俩
let's start putting our own families first.
还是各自以家庭为重吧
Does it feel good?
感觉很好吧？
Does it feel good
信誓旦旦要重建婚姻
making a pledge…
自我感觉…
to rebuild your marriage?
很好吧？
Ichiko.
一子
I need to ask to avoid any future issues.
为了避免以后造成任何麻烦 我想确认一下
I can go all the way today, right?
今天我可以进行到底 对吧？
Yes.
对
Please.
拜托了
Mitsuki?
美月？
Mitsuki, why?
美月 为什么？
I…
我…
I guess I'm the kind of person who would do this.
我猜我就是这种人
Otoya, I…
二也 我…
I really loved
我真的很喜欢你
and hated you so much.
也很讨厌你
Even after we break up,
即使我们分手了
I don't want you to have sex with anyone else.
我也不愿你和别人上床
I'm so sorry, Otoya. It hurts, right?
真的很抱歉 二也 很疼吧？
Yeah. A lot.
好疼
It feels good, right?
很舒服吧？
It feels good.
很舒服
The bleeding isn't stopping.
血还没止住
It will. It will stop. I think it will.
会止住的 应该会的
Why don't I get an ambulance?
还是叫救护车吧？
You can't.
不能叫
It will be bad for both of us if this becomes a big deal.
如果事情闹大 对我们俩都没好处
Mitsuki.
美月
Go home.
你回家吧
-But-- -I'll be fine.
-可是… -我没事
Mitsuki.
美月
Take care of yourself.
你多保重
Otoya.
二也
Just go.
快走吧
Go. I'll be okay.
走吧 我没事
Okay.
好
Fuck, it hurts.
疼死了
I can't die.
我不能死
I won't die, Ichiko.
我不会死的 小一
Thanks for booking me.
感谢你这次指名我
No, thank you.
不 谢谢你
I'm really happy I did.
我很高兴选了你
Thank you.
谢谢
-Cheers.
-干杯
It's hard for me to come when I'm nervous,
我紧张时很难达到高潮
but I orgasmed right away.
但今天很快就高潮了
I knew it. You're really good.
你果然很厉害
It's not just sex.
不光是性爱
I haven't touched anyone,
我已经很长时间
or shared loving kisses,
没和人有过肢体接触
or hugged someone in a really long time.
或者拥抱、亲吻了
I felt it, not just with my body, but also deep in my soul.
不光我的身体感受到 我的灵魂也深深感受到了
It was phenomenal.
真的很不可思议
Ichiko.
一子
Sorry.
对不起
Here. Tissue.
来 纸巾
-Thanks. -Sure.
谢谢
Want some water?
想喝点水吗？
Here.
给
Is your marriage,
你的婚姻
what you'd call, sexless?
是所谓的无性婚姻吗？
You can call it that.
可以这么说吧
It's been about two years, I guess.
大概两年前开始的
I see.
是这样啊
It was originally because I didn't want to do it.
一开始是因为我不愿意
So my husband found a lover,
于是我丈夫就在外面找了个情人
and I accepted it.
我也接受了
Since I had absolutely no sex drive
因为我完全没有性欲
and aside from sex, our relationship was really good.
而除了性方面之外 我们的夫妻关系非常好
I thought that things would be okay like this,
我原本觉得这样安排挺好的
so I did nothing to change it.
所以就听之任之
And now here I am, doing this.
结果却变成了现在这样
I didn't do this to get back at my husband
我这么做不是为了报复我丈夫
but I think a part of me wanted revenge.
但我觉得从某种程度上说 我确实想报复
But when I actually did it, it was better than expected.
但等到真的做了 才发现原来感觉这么好
And made me realize sex really is amazing.
这让我意识到 性爱真的很美妙
Our relationship is messy and weird, right? Even though we're married.
我们的关系很奇怪吧？虽然是夫妻
I have never been married, so it's not for me to say.
我没结过婚 所以没有发言权
But listening to what you just said…
但听你这么说…
I think you simply hate it, right?
感觉你其实很讨厌这样吧？
That your husband has a lover.
讨厌你丈夫有情人
Why don't you tell him?
你为什么不告诉他呢？
But…
可是…
it's too late now.
现在已经太晚了
It's never too late.
永远都不会太晚
He's your husband.
他是你的丈夫
Here. Blow your nose.
来 擤擤鼻子
Thank you.
谢谢
But…
可是…
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办
He turned me down
之前我想和他亲热
when I tried to sleep with him before.
但被他拒绝了
He did?
是吗？
I see.
这样啊
But
不过
sex isn't only about penetration.
性爱和插入未必是一回事
BASED ON THE MANGA "1122" BY PEKO WATANABE
（根据渡边平子同名漫画改编）
1122: FOR A HAPPY MARRIAGE
电视剧名：1122 好夫妻
Hello, I'm from the front desk.
你好 我是酒店前台
Yeah.
好
I'm opening the door.
我要开门了
Pardon me. I'm coming in.
打扰了 我进来了
I'm really sorry.
真的很抱歉
I wanted your help.
请帮帮我
I see. Okay.
好的
Please use this.
请用这个
Sorry I made a mess.
抱歉弄脏了
Don't mind it.
没关系
Please lie down.
您先躺一下
You'll be fine. You're in good hands.
没关系 请放心交给我吧
Are you okay? I have a taxi waiting at the back door.
您还好吗？ 我叫了出租车 正在后门等着
Thank you.
谢谢
I'm really sorry about this.
真的很抱歉
You don't need to apologize.
您不必道歉
I've seen worse at the previous hotel I worked for.
在之前工作的酒店 我见过更惨的
Worse than this?
比这还惨？
Yes.
对啊
Besides,
再说了
sir, you are still alive.
先生 您还活着呢
URGENT CARE CENTER
（急诊）
This has got to hurt.
一定很疼吧
Yes, it hurts.
确实很疼
How did this happen?
怎么弄的？
I tripped and…
我绊了一跤…
the kenzan happened to be right there.
刚好磕在剑山上
Kenzan?
剑山？
It's used in ikebana.
插花用的
Then it will be bad if it gets infected
要是伤口感染就糟了
by the bacteria in the plants.
花草上有细菌
I think it will be okay.
我觉得应该不要紧
-Really? -It was a brand new kenzan.
那个剑山是新的
Was it?
是吗？
Then I'll give you antibiotics and painkillers.
那我给你开点抗生素和止痛药
Okay.
好
Rest here while the medicine takes its effect.
在这里休息一会儿 等药起效
Wow. This has really got to hurt.
肯定疼死了
Doctor.
医生
Yes?
嗯？
Can I…
我还能…
Will it still function properly?
以后功能还会正常吗？
Function?
功能？
Oh, erection?
勃起吗？
Yeah.
是的
Physically, there is no problem.
生理上没问题
Physically…
生理上…
that type of thing is, you know…
这种事嘛…
If you experience issues, the cause will be psychological.
如果有困难 那就是心理原因
Weren't you scared?
当时很害怕吧？
OTOYA AIHARA - I GOT TREATED AT THE HOSPITAL AND I'M OKAY
（相原二也 我去医院治疗了 没事）
Then contact me if you need anything.
有什么需要 尽管联系我
Even if it's just to talk.
哪怕只是聊聊天
This.
这个
It's like my business card.
是我的名片
Thanks.
谢谢
So, may fortune favor you.
那么 祝你好运
Good luck.
加油
Bye.
再见
REI - TO ICHIKO, THANKS FOR TODAY
（礼 至一子 今天多谢了 下次再指名我哦）
What should I do with my sorrow?
面对这样的悲伤 我该怎么办？
Who will be the one to save me?
谁来拯救我？
I'm Romeo and you're my Juliet
我是罗密欧 你是我的朱丽叶
This is a freaking pain in my ass
这真是个大麻烦
I wanna hold you in my arms
我想将你抱在怀里
I wanna watch you as you sleep
我想看你熟睡的脸
I wanna eat the meals you make
我想吃你做的食物
Whether I'm sent east or west
无论往东还是往西
It's all a freaking pain in my ass
这都是个很大的麻烦
I'm home.
我回来了
Welcome back.
你回来啦
Hey, Otoyan.
二也
Can we talk right now?
我们现在能谈谈吗？
Now might not be a good time.
现在有点不方便
Sorry. My back is hurting again.
抱歉 我的腰又疼了
Really? Are you okay?
是吗？你还好吧？
Yeah. I took some medicine.
嗯 已经吃过药了
I'll just sleep it off.
睡一觉就会好的
Okay.
好吧
Otoyan, happy birthday.
二也 生日快乐
Good night.
晚安
Thanks. Good night.
谢谢 晚安
Is Hiro asleep?
小宏睡了吗？
He fell asleep on the way home from my mom's.
从我妈家回来的路上就睡着了
He's sleeping soundly.
睡得很沉
How was your day, Mitsuki?
你今天过得怎么样 美月？
Wasn't it your last flower class?
今天是你最后一堂花道课吧？
Today was the last class.
今天是最后一次
But the ikebana class…
但你想问的…
isn't what you're really asking about, is it?
并不是花道课吧？
Shiro.
志朗
You knew I was having an affair. Right?
你知道我有外遇吧？
Why don't you sit here?
过来坐下吧
I knew.
我知道
That is why I asked if it was over.
所以我才问有没有结束
I ended it.
已经结束了
But
可是
I stabbed him.
我把他刺伤了
What did you just say?
你说什么？
Oh, but it was with a kenzan flower base.
但用的是剑山
What are you saying?
你到底在胡说什么？
I'm wondering that myself.
我也觉得荒唐
What is the point of making up such a lie?
说这种谎有什么意义？
You really stabbed him?
你真的把人刺伤了？
Is he okay?
他还好吗？
He told me he went to the hospital and is okay.
他说去了医院 已经没事了
-So you can relax. -No.
你大可放心
That is not important.
重点不是这个
Why did you do it?
你为什么那么做？
I…
我…
I didn't think you were that stupid.
真没想到你居然那么傻
Really?
是吗？
You've been taking me for an idiot this entire time.
一直以来 你不也把我当成傻瓜
Are you saying it's my fault?
你是在怪我吗？
No.
不是
I'm responsible for the stupid things I've done.
我做过的傻事 我自己负责
And it won't create any problems for you.
不会连累到你
Isn't that what you wanted?
你不就想这样吗？
Go ahead. You can hit me.
没关系 你可以打我
I won't hit you.
我不会打你
Because I love you.
因为我爱你
Even if you're the type to stab the man she loves…
哪怕你会刺伤你爱的男人
I will not hit the woman I love.
我也不会打我心爱的女人
Ouch. Ouch.
好疼
Are the pain meds working?
是止痛药起作用了吗？
Good morning.
早上好
You're up early today.
你今天起得真早
I had a rush job so I got up early.
要赶工 所以起得早
Want some coffee?
想喝咖啡吗？
Yeah, thanks.
想 谢谢
Is your back okay?
你的腰还好吗？
Can you go to work?
能去上班吗？
Anyway, Otoyan.
对了 二也
Did you notice anything?
你没注意到什么吗？
Like what?
什么？
This. It's your birthday present.
这个 你的生日礼物
I left it on the table for you yesterday.
我昨天放在桌子上了
Sorry. I didn't see it.
对不起 我没看到
Open it.
打开吧
Mount Fuji sake cups.
富士山的清酒杯
So cute. Thank you.
真可爱 谢谢你
I bought sake too.
我还买了清酒哦
See?
你看
Want to drink it together tonight?
今晚想一起喝吗？
I'm only working until the afternoon so I'll make something to go with it.
我今天下午就能把工作忙完 到时候准备些下酒菜
What would you like?
你想吃什么？
Sorry, Ichiko.
抱歉 小一
Since I'm still not feeling good,
我身体还不太舒服
I'll take a rain check.
所以还是改天吧
That sake looks like it will be good.
这清酒看起来很好喝
You can drink it yourself.
小一你自己喝吧
I'll go get ready for work.
我准备去上班了
That's not what I meant, Otoyan.
不是这样的 二也
I bought it because I wanted to drink it with you.
我买来就是想和你一起喝的
Oh, of course.
这样哦
I'm sorry.
对不起
Thank you.
谢谢你
Let's drink it when I get better.
那等我好些再一起喝吧
This is Otoya. How are you?
您好 我是相原
I'm not feeling well, so I won't attend the meeting.
我今天身体不舒服 就不来开会了
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
很抱歉 给您添麻烦了
I'll look at the meeting notes tomorrow.
我明天会看会议记录
Yes. Yes. Thank you.
好 谢谢您
Bye.
再见
TOKYO - WHERE TO KILL TIME
（东京 打发时间的去处）
PERFECT FOR COUPLES - 23 PLACES TO HAVE A DATE
（适合情侣 23个约会场所）
10 SPOTS IN TOKYO THAT WILL GET YOUR BODY MOVING
（东京10处能让您舒展筋骨的景点）
[TOKYO] 8 HIDDEN SPOTS TO RECHARGE AND RELAX
（东京 八个放松身心的 小众宝藏地）
FOR THE GAPS IN YOUR ITINERARY! MAKE YOUR TRIP TO TOKYO MORE FUN
（行程空闲时的好去处！ 让东京之行乐趣翻倍）
TOKYO SPACE &amp; SCIENCE MUSEUM
（东京宇宙科学馆）
VIEW THE STARRY SKY IN A 18M DIAMETER PLANETARIUM
（在直径18米的天文馆观赏星空）
Here, in a city like Tokyo,
在东京这样的城市
the building and street lights are so bright and strong
城市灯光太强
that it's become harder to see the stars.
难以看到星空
But what if we turn off all the city and factory lights
但如果照亮天空的城市灯光
that brighten the skies?
和工厂灯光都熄灭了
What will the night sky look like?
夜空会是什么样呢？
A beautiful starry sky is constantly shining above our heads like this.
我们的头顶上 一直有这样一片美丽的星空
Now if you look around the sky,
现在 如果你环视天空
you can already see the spring constellations
东方的天空中 已经可以看到春季星座缓缓升起
rising up in the eastern sky.
那颗明亮的星是织女星
It looks so good!
好漂亮啊！
Right?
是吧？
This one is done.
这个烤好了
-Here. -Thanks.
-来 -谢谢
Hot.
烫
Food grilled on an open flame is so tasty.
明火烤的东西真好吃
But don't you think we bought too much food?
但我们是不是买太多食材了？
It should be okay.
应该没关系
-It will be okay? -Yeah.
-没关系吗？ -嗯
Rain?
下雨了？
-It's raining.
-下雨了
-It's raining hard. What's going on? -Oh, no.
-下大了 怎么回事？ -糟了
-Evacuate. Evacuate. -Wait, what?
-快撤 -什么？
-Evacuate. Our stuff. -Our things.
-快撤 我们的东西 -拿东西
Hold on.
等等
What should we do?
我们怎么办？
Crap.
哎呀
Sorry.
对不起
Wow.
安全了
-Oh, my God. -Oh, my…
-天呐 -我的天…
-A sudden heavy shower? -It's really raining.
-突然下大雨？ -下得好大
Hey, isn't it leaking?
这里面是不是漏雨？
Well, it's a mesh tent.
是网线的帐篷
Are all tents like this?
所有帐篷都这样吗？
No, there is a covering for it.
不是 外面有盖的
-Then let's use it. -I left it at home.
-那就盖上吧 -放家里了
Why?
为什么？
I thought it would make it hot. And it's bulky.
我觉得盖了闷气 而且太占地方
-You idiot. -But I have a raincoat.
-笨蛋 -但我有件雨衣
-A raincoat? -Yeah, raincoat. Hold on.
-雨衣？ -对 雨衣 等一下
-Raincoat, raincoat. -Raincoat.
-雨衣
-Here. The raincoat. -Thanks.
-给 雨衣 -谢谢
We should go take cover somewhere.
我们找个地方避雨吧
-Right, take cover. -Let's go.
-对 避雨 -我们走
-Where to? -This way.
-去哪儿？ -这边
-How about there? -Okay.
-那里怎么样？ -好
-That way. -The meat.
-那边 -肉
-Oh, the meat. -Well…
-哎呀
-But the meat. -The poor meat.
-好可惜
You know.
说起来
Since we're beginners at this,
我们是初学者
we should have gone somewhere easy, like a place with a cottage.
本该找个更容易的地方 比如小木屋之类的
I suggested some places like that,
我提议去木屋来着
but you said no since there will be college students there partying.
可你嫌那儿会有大学生开派对
What? I did?
什么？我有吗？
You did. That's why I looked for a quiet spot and came here.
有啊 所以我才找了 这么个人迹罕至的地方
Oh, okay.
这样啊
Otoyan.
二也
-Come here. Come on. -What?
过来 快来
What is it?
怎么了？
That. Look.
你看
Beautiful.
好美
Yeah, it's beautiful.
是很美
Is that the Milky Way?
那就是银河吗？
This trip was a total mess, but it was still fun.
这次宿营很失败 但我还是好开心
I really loved Ichiko's candidness,
我很喜欢小一的坦率和坚强
her strength, the way she lives life at her own pace,
她按照自己的节奏行事
and how she finds fun in everything.
在生活中随处能发现乐趣
Even back then.
那时就是如此
To the west, you can see a pale band of light that looks like a cloud.
在西方 有一条苍白的光带 看上去就像薄薄的云层
It is the Milky Way.
那就是银河
But thinking about it now,
但现在想来
when she said it was fun on that day,
那天她说开心
it was her way of being kind and telling me
其实是体贴我 她是在告诉我
it was okay that I screwed up.
虽然我搞砸了 但没关系
The shape of the Milky Way we see is from our perspective inside the…
这是从银河系内部看到的形态…
I can easily think of a few times she acted as if she was enjoying herself
她怕我难过 所以表现出开心的样子 像这样的情况
so I wouldn't be hurt.
我很容易就能想起好多次
Ichiko has always been really good to me.
小一一直对我很好
I'm back, Ichiko.
我回来了 小一
I wasn't feeling good so I left early.
因为不舒服就早点下班了
But somehow,
可不知怎的
I started feeling better on my way home and could do some shopping.
回家路上感觉好起来 于是就去购物了
I got a couple of things.
我买了好些东西
Look.
你看
Dried mullet roe.
干乌鱼子
And simmered whale with ginger.
还有姜炖鲸鱼肉
So, Ichiko.
所以 小一
Let's drink that sake you got me for my birthday.
我们一起来喝 你为我庆生买的清酒吧
What's wrong?
你怎么了？
What about you, Otoyan? What's wrong?
二也你呢？你怎么了？
What do you mean?
你指什么？
Did you get hurt?
你受伤了吗？
Hurt?
受伤？
I found a bloody gauze in the bathroom trash can.
我在卫生间垃圾桶里 发现一块带血的纱布
Oh, right.
哦 那个啊
Yesterday, I tripped and cut myself coming home.
昨天 我回家路上摔了一跤 划破了
Where?
哪里？
On my leg. Around here.
腿上 这里
Show me.
给我看
You don't have to look at it. It's not a big deal, really.
没那个必要 小伤而已
Otoyan.
二也
You left this paper bag on the balcony, didn't you?
这个纸袋是你放在阳台上的吧？
It was filled with bloody clothes.
里面的衣服上都是血迹
You didn't have a client dinner yesterday.
你昨天不是和客户吃饭
You went to see her, right?
而是去见那个女人了吧？
Sorry. I looked at your phone.
对不起 我看了你的手机
What happened?
发生了什么事？
No more lies.
别再骗我了
Otoyan.
二也
I want you to tell me the truth.
请你对我说实话
Like you said…
你说得没错
I saw her yesterday.
昨天我去见她了
I'm sorry I lied.
对不起 我撒了谎
You probably won't believe me,
你可能不会相信
but I was going to end things with her.
但我是去和她分手的
And then…
然后…
yesterday,
昨天
I met her at the hotel.
我和她在酒店见面
And…
然后…
She stabbed me with a kenzan.
她用剑山刺伤了我
Where?
哪里？
My genitals.
私处
Sorry, Otoyan.
对不起 二也
I'm so sorry.
真的很对不起
Why are you apologizing?
你为什么道歉？
Don't do that.
不用这样
You shouldn't be apologizing like one of those wives
不要像电视剧里演的那样
with a cheating husband in a drama.
丈夫出轨了 妻子却要道歉
I'm the one that's wrong.
犯错的人是我
No.
不是的
It's a problem between us,
这是我们俩之间的问题
but I'm the only one who ignored it and made you deal with it alone.
但我却无动于衷 让你一个人面对
So you ended up getting hurt.
所以你才会受伤
I was the one…
是我…
who told you to have an affair.
我让你去外面找女人
But I couldn't take back my words
说了这种话 又没办法反悔
because I thought
因为我觉得
it was ugly to be jealous.
善妒会很难看
I couldn't accept my feelings
我不能面对自己的感受
and was too proud and stubborn, so I didn't say anything.
太固执 又放不下面子 所以我什么都不说
But that made me even more confused.
但心里却更乱了
I tried to tell myself that everything was okay, but…
我试图说服自己没关系 可是…
I finally realized
我终于意识到
I hated the idea of you having a relationship
我真的不希望你和别人
with someone else.
发生关系
So I thought I had to tell you how I felt.
所以我觉得应该把我的感受告诉你
Really. It's so hard to be honest and tell you about my feelings.
真的 坦白说出自己的感受真的好难
Don't cry, Ichiko.
别哭 小一
When you're in pain, I'm in pain.
你难过 我就会难过
Ichiko.
小一
Thank you for telling me the truth.
谢谢你对我说出心里话
I'm really happy right now.
我现在非常高兴
I…
我…
I had given up.
我本来已经放弃了
Actually, I stopped thinking about ever sleeping with you again.
我原本以为这辈子 都不会再和你亲热了
I apologize for what I did in the past.
以前是我错了 对不起
No, I didn't mean to bring that up again.
不 我没打算翻旧账
But now,
但现在
I…
我…
really want to
真的很想
make love to you.
和你做爱
That makes me so incredibly happy.
我真的好开心啊
Right now…
现在…
I'm injured, but…
我身上有伤 但是…
Ichiko.
小一
Let's start doing it again when I get better.
等我好了 我们就重新开始做吧
Welcome back.
你回来了
Didn't I tell you to go to bed first since I'll be late?
我不是说了会晚回 让你先睡吗？
But I couldn't sleep anyway.
可我睡不着
Shiro.
志朗
I want to talk.
我想和你谈谈
About?
谈什么？
Yesterday's conversation.
昨天谈的事
Didn't you break up?
你不是跟他断了吗？
I'll forget about it. Don't bring it up again.
我会忘记这事 你也别再提了
I broke up with him,
我和他结束了
but not with you.
但我和你并没结束
I'm tired. Let's talk next time.
我累了 改天再说吧
Thirty minutes is fine, so please.
30分钟就好 拜托了
If we run away instead of talking about it now,
如果现在避而不谈
we'll never fix our marriage, even if I ended my affair.
那就算婚外情结束了 我们也无法修补夫妻关系
Mitsuki,
美月
what do you want from me?
你想让我怎样？
You said you still love me, right?
你说你还爱着我 对不对？
Even after what I did?
哪怕我做了那种事？
But you're only seeing the part of me that you want to see.
但你看到的我 只是你想看到的那一面
Then did he see the whole you, love you, and accept you?
那他就看到了全部的你 他爱你 并且接受你？
Is that why you lied to your family and snuck around with him?
所以你才对家人撒谎 跟他苟且？
Had sex with him?
跟他上床？
I admit I was weak, and what I did was wrong.
我承认我软弱 我做错了
But I want to talk about our future.
但我想谈谈我们的未来
Stop it.
住手
Stop.
别这样
No. Stop.
不 不要
I said stop!
我叫你停下！
Shut up.
别喊了
Ouch.
疼
You've gotten pretty violent.
你现在变得这么暴力
What about your violence?
那你自己呢？
Even if we're married, forcing sex is rape.
哪怕是夫妻 强迫发生性行为就是强奸
Now you're acting like a feminist?
怎么说起女权主义的话了？
Did you learn about human rights during your affair?
搞外遇时 学会了人权？
I really hate how you protect your own feelings by always looking down
我讨厌你总是为了保护自己
on other people.
就取笑别人
I'm going to bed.
我去睡了
Shiro.
志朗
I want you…
我希望你…
to see me as a human being.
把我当成一个有血有肉的人
We have to change,
我们必须做出改变
both you and I.
你我都要改变
If we don't,
否则
then I can't be with you.
我们就不能在一起了
Ouch.
好疼
Watching Otoyan as he slept peacefully,
看着二也平静的睡颜
I kept thinking about what I did yesterday.
我一直在想我昨天做的事
When Otoyan was stabbed in the genitals,
二也的私处被刺伤时
I was having crazy hot sex
我正在和风俗店的男公关
with a gigolo from the brothel.
交欢缠绵
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.
（本故事纯属虚构）
Subtitle: Annie Chen
字幕翻译：纪小敏